<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SkySync</string>
    <string name="splash_image">Moon image</string>
    <string name="slogan">Sync with the sky, stay ahead, come rain or shine</string>
    <string name="back_arrow">Back arrow</string>
    <string name="search_icon">Search icon</string>
    <string name="more_icon">More icon</string>
    <string name="condition">condition</string>
    <string name="humidity">humidity</string>
    <string name="week">Weekly</string>
    <string name="weather_icon">weather icon</string>
    <string name="rain_percentage">rain percentage</string>
    <string name="about_welcome_title">Welcome to Sky Sync!</string>

    <string name="about_welcome">
        At Sky Sync, we believe in making weather information not just accessible but delightful.
        Our mission is to provide you with accurate and up-to-the-minute weather updates,
        ensuring you are always prepared for whatever Mother Nature has in store.</string>
    <string name="about_key_features">Key Features:</string>
    <string name="about_key_features_1">
        Real-time Weather Updates: Stay ahead of the weather with our real-time forecasts.
        Whether it iss sunny skies, stormy clouds, or a chance of rain, Sky Sync keeps you in the know.
        Global Coverage: Wherever you are, we have got you covered. Access weather information for any location worldwide,
        so you can plan your day, whether it is a local outing or an international adventure.
    </string>
    <string name="about_key_features_2">
        Global Coverage: Wherever you are, we have got you covered. Access weather information for any location worldwide,
        so you can plan your day, whether it is a local outing or an international adventure.
    </string>
    <string name="about_key_features_3">
        Intuitive Design: Our user-friendly interface makes navigating through weather data a breeze.
        Elegant visuals and easy-to-understand graphics ensure you get the information you need with just a glance.

    </string>
    <string name="about_why_title">Why Sky Sync:</string>
    <string name="about_why">
        Sky Sync is not just a weather app; it is your reliable weather companion.
        We are dedicated to delivering a seamless and enjoyable weather experience,
        helping you make informed decisions and adding a touch of sunshine to your day.
    </string>

    <string name="change_units">"Change Units of Measurement"</string>


</resources>